

# ALEKSANDRA RYBOŁOWICZ

#### JUNIOR FRONTEND DEVELOPER

I am a mechatronics engineer with almost 3 years of professional experience in movie postproduction and a self taught illustrator/animator. Currently I am focused on gaining my frontend developer experience in React.js, HTML & CSS and JavaScript.

## DETAILS

Warsaw, Poland +48 513 318 222 olarybolowicz@gmail.com

# LINKS





in LinkedIn



Portfolio

# SKILLS

- Html & CSS
- JavaScript
- React.js
- C++
- OpenCV
- Django
- Python

# HOBBIES

Animation & illustration, Cinematography

## EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### DiFactory - DI Specialist

September 2019 - June 2022

- Conforming and mastering feature films and TV series
- Data management on film set
- Technical quality control of video content
- Creating a Django app generating FFMPEG code for video conversion
- · Working with Python scripts automating daily processes

#### TVN Grupa Discovery - Internship

March 2019 - May 2019

- Assisting production manager in estimating production budget and booking camera equipment
- · Data management

## EDUCATION

#### Bachelor of Mechatronics, Warsaw University of Technology

October 2016 - February 2021

- Specialization: Multimedia Technologies
- Engineering Thesis: Recognizing Art Movement With the Use of Computer Technologies

As a part of my engineering thesis I have developed an image processing application written in C++ with the use of OpenCV library. With the help of statistics analysis tools I have created four classification models representing different art movements. So the application can process any painting and predict it's most probable art movement.

## PROJECTS

#### Bookie.

Web application for book lovers built using React.js, Node.js backend, Google Books API, React Router, React Context and Firebase.

#### **Ivory**

Fully responsive online clothing shop landing page with shopping cart functionality made with JavaScript, HTML, CSS.